Guide to the Mix Collection 1970-2001 (Bulk 1987-2001) MSS 143
© 2012 Fales Library and Special Collections
- SERIES VII: 1993
  - Subseries G: Media
    - Title: [1.]--Butterfly Potion [2.]--Dick Johnson [3.]--Lesbians of Russia, Jimmy [4.]--Little Fury Things (Box 4, Folder ID: 143.1133)
      Old number: K7d, V.12.8783
      Director: Spring, Jim and Jurgensen, Jens
    - Title: Voice (Box 4, Folder ID: 143.1134)
      Old number: K7d, V.12.8786
      Director: Turcotte, James
    - Title: M.M. In Motion (Box 4, Folder ID: 143.1135)
      Old number: K7d, V.12.8787
      Director: Ostrovsky, Vivian
    - Title: Family Diaries, 1969-75 (Box 4, Folder ID: 143.1136)
      Old number: K7d, V.12.8789
    - Title: Mind is the Medium (Box 4, Folder ID: 143.1137)
      Old number: K7d, V.12.8790
      Director: Carman, James
    - Title: The Brenda and Glennda Show: [1.]--ACT-UP/Target Bush [2.]--Wigstock '91, Screened: 1992 (Box 4, Folder ID: 143.1138)
      Old number: K7d, V.12.8795
      Director: [1.]--Wentzy, James
      Duration: 160 minutes
    - Title: AIDS Community Television: Target Bush, Screened: 1992 (Box 5, Folder ID: 143.1139)
      Old number: K7d, V.12.8795.C2
      Director: Wentzy, James
    - Title: Mas'ter-ba-shen (Box 5, Folder ID: 143.1140)
      Old number: 41, K7d, V.12.8796
      Director: Spitzer, John Eric
    - Title: Two Spirits Speak Out (Box 5, Folder ID: 143.1141)
      Old number: K7d, V.12.8797
    - Title: "Trajectoires et passages"": Women Filmmakers in the Avant-Garde - 1980-1990 [1.]--Grapholetti [2.]--Choreographie [3.]--Stories [4.]--USSA [5.]--Mansfield K. [6.]--IN/SIDE/OUT I-VI, [1.]--Screened: 1991 [6.]--Screened: 1988 (Box 5, Folder ID: 143.1142)
      Old number: K7d, V.12.8798
      Director: [1.]--Thomas, Francoise [2.]--Thirache, Marcelle [3.]--Fontaine, Cecile [4.]--Ostrovsky, Vivian [5.]--Rousset, Martine [6.]--Burford, Jennifer
      Duration: 150 minutes
    - Title: Medea - A Girl Just Like You (Box 5, Folder ID: 143.1143)
      Old number: K7d, V.12.8800
      Director: Schicker, Eva
    - Title: [Russian title] (Box 5, Folder ID: 143.1144)
      Old number: 4, 49091, DIII 1C, V.12.8878
      Director: [Russian credits]
    - Title: Be Good, My Children (Box 5, Folder ID: 143.1145)
      Old number: K7b, V.12.8986
      Director: Chang, Christine
    - Title: [1.]--Work-in-Progress [2.]--The Natural Order (Box 5, Folder ID: 143.1146)
      Old number: EII3c, V.12.9101.C1
      Director: Mertes, Cara
    - Title: Bald Diva luv, Screened: 1993 (Box 5, Folder ID: 143.1147)
      Old number: V.12.9170
      Director: Johnson, Vanessa
      Distributor: performers: [listed on tape container]
      Duration: 5 minutes
    - Title: Homophobia Is Known To Cause Nightmares, Screened: 1993 (Box 5, Folder ID: 143.1148)
      Old number: EII3e, V.12.9171
      Director: Handelman, Michelle
    - Title: Together Alone, Screened: 1991 (Box 5, Folder ID: 143.1149)
      Old number: EII3e, V.12.9175
      Director: Castellaneta, P.J.
    - Title: Smoke (Box 5, Folder ID: 143.1150)
      Old number: EII3f, V.12.9192
      Director: D'Auria, Mark
    - Title: Tomboychik, Screened: 1993 (Box 5, Folder ID: 143.1151)
      Old number: EII3a, V.12.9219
      Director: DuBowski, Sandi
    - Title: [1.]--Mary Magdaline [2.]--L'Amour Fou, [2.]--Screened: 1992 (Box 5, Folder ID: 143.1152)
      Old number: EII3a, V.12.9220
      Director: Serra, M.M.
    - Title: [1.]--The Dreaming [2.]--Man Act/Sweatlodge [3.]--Step We Gaily [4.]--Amelia Rose Towers [5.]--Against the Inhuman Undershadow of the Lynch Mob, [1, 3, 4, 5.]--Screened: 1993 (Box 5, Folder ID: 143.1153)
      Old number: EII4d, V.34U.6401
      Director: [1.]--Thomas, Ifan [3.]--Broadbent, Lucinda [4.]--Farkas, Jackie [5.]--De Oliveira, Rogerio
      Format: 3/4 in. Umatic
      Duration:
    - Title: Voi Che Sapete, Screened: 1993 (Box 5, Folder ID: 143.1154)
      Old number: EII4b, V.34U.6403
      Duration: [5 minutes]
    - Title: Sleeplessness (Box 5, Folder ID: 143.1155)
      Old number: EII4b, V.34U.6404
    - Title: Find Your G Spot: [How] To Female Ejaculate (Box 5, Folder ID: 143.1156)
      Old number: EII4b, V.34U.6405
      Director: Murphy, Melissa
    - Title: Waves of a Distant Shore (Box 5, Folder ID: 143.1157)
      Old number: EII4b, V.34U.6407
      Director: Ong, Meng
    - Title: The New Dark Ages, Screened: 1993 (Box 6, Folder ID: 143.1158)
      Old number: EII4b, V.34U.6408
      Director: Tomasino, Walter and Giuliano, Steven
    - Title: [1.]--No Money, No Honey [2.]--Lovin' In My Oven [3.]--Cholita in No Controles [4.]--That Fertile Feeling [5.]--It All Started In Black, [4.]--Screened: 1995 (Box 6, Folder ID: 143.1159)
      Old number: EII4b, V.34U.6409
      Director: O'Shea, John [4.]--Davis, Vaginal Crème
    - Title: Lilies, Screened: 1993 (Box 6, Folder ID: 143.1160)
      Old number: EII4b, V.34U.6410
      Director: O'Malley, John
    - Title: Video Boyfriend (Box 6, Folder ID: 143.1161)
      Old number: EII4b, V.34U.6414
      Director: Ellis, Andrew
    - Title: Theory on a Stick (Box 6, Folder ID: 143.1162)
      Old number: V.34U.6415
      Director: Murrah, Natalie
    - Title: Little League Lee (Box 6, Folder ID: 143.1163)
      Old number: EII4d, V.34U.6460
      Director: Gerstein, Lee
    - Title: Light on the Path (Box 6, Folder ID: 143.1164)
      Old number: EII4d, V.34U.6458
      Distributor: distributed by: Motus Film and Video
    - Title: [1.]--Kachapati (Spray the Wall) [2.]--The Pervert Explores An Instant, [2.]--Screened: 1993 (Box 6, Folder ID: 143.1165)
      Old number: EII4d, V.34U.6459
      Director: Wright, Georgia B.
    - Title: [1.]--Boobs [2.]--Condoms Are A Girl's Best Friend (Box 6, Folder ID: 143.1166)
      Old number: 198, EII4d, V.34U.6461
    - Title: Our Fanzine Friends Part 1 (Box 6, Folder ID: 143.1167)
      Old number: EII4d, V.34U.6463 1/2
    - Title: Our Fanzine Friends Part 2: [1.]--Spring Break [2.]--Streetwalker Fashion/Fertile Latoya Jackson Video Mag, [2.]--Screened: 1993 (Box 6, Folder ID: 143.1168)
      Old number: EII4d, V.34U.6463 2/2
      Director: [2.]--Castro, Rick
      Distributor: performers: [2.]--[listed in 1993 program, includes Vaginal Davis]
    - Title: The Ideal/Na(rra)tion (Box 7, Folder ID: 143.1169)
      Old number: K7c, V.34U.8754
      Director: Ching, Yau
    - Title: Drawing the Line (Box 7, Folder ID: 143.1170)
      Old number: K7c, V.34.8755
      Director: Boschman, Lorna
    - Title: [1.]--The Language Of Boys [2.]--A Gorme's Delight (Box 7, Folder ID: 143.1171)
      Old number: EII3c, V.34U.9122.C1
      Director: Christopher, Mark
    - Title: The Salt Mines (Box 7, Folder ID: 143.1172)
      Old number: EII3d, V.34.9140.C1
      Director: Aikin, Susana and Aparicio, Carlos
    - Title: Postcards From America (Box 7, Folder ID: 143.1173)
      Old number: EII3e, V.34.9160.C1
    - Title: Edit Master / Gay and Lesbian Experimental Film Program Fanzine Pt. 1 (Box 7, Folder ID: 143.1174)
      Old number: EII3f, V.34.9176
    - Title: Pt. 2 Fanzine Master [1.]--Spring Break [2.]--Streetwalker (Box 7, Folder ID: 143.1175)
      Old number: EII3f, V.34U.9177
      Distributor: distributed by: Valkhn Film and Video, Inc.
    - Title: Strut (Box 7, Folder ID: 143.1176)
      Old number: 51949, EII3f, V.34U.9178
      Director: DeRuiter, Heidi
    - Title: Medea -- Just A Girl Like You (Box 7, Folder ID: 143.1177)
      Old number: EII3f, V.34.9188
    - Title: Palingenesis (Box 7, Folder ID: 143.1178)
      Old number: EII3a, V.34U.9214
      Director: Martinez, Juan Carlos
    - Title: Sex Wars [1.]--I Am A Man, But… [2.]--He-She-Pee [3.]--Mr. Wonderful, [3.]--Screened: 1995 (Box 7, Folder ID: 143.1179)
      Old number: EII3a, V.34U.9216
      Director: [3.]--Malkames, Marlise
    - Title: [1.]--Requiem [2.]--Spin Cycle [3.]--Fag Solos, Screened: [1993] [more yellow tape in boxes 47-53] [2.]--Screened: 1991 (Box 8, Folder ID: 143.1258)
      Old number: EII4e, V.12.6487
      Director: [2.]--Burch, Aarin
      Format: EII4e, V.12.6487
    - Title: Tucumcari Tonite, Screened: [1993]. [more yellow tape in boxes 47-53] (Box 8, Folder ID: 143.1259)
      Old number: EII4e, V.12.6489, 248
      Director: Benson, Suzanne
      Format: EII4e, V.12.6489, 248
    - Title: Bill and Ted's Homosexual Adventure, Screened: [1993]. [more yellow tape in boxes 47-53] (Box 8, Folder ID: 143.1260)
      Old number: EII4f, V.12.6499.C2, 68
      Distributor: performers: Pansy Division
      Format: EII4f, V.12.6499.C2, 68
    - Title: Stroke of Luck, Screened: [1993]. [more yellow tape in boxes 47-53] (Box 8, Folder ID: 143.1261)
      Old number: EII4f, V.12.6508, 302
      Director: Steffen, James
      Format: EII4f, V.12.6508, 302
    - Title: EII4f V.12.6509 [case only, no videocassette] (Box 8, Folder ID: 143.1262)
      Old number: EII4f, V.12.6509
      Format: EII4f, V.12.6509
      Duration: N/A
    - Title: At Home With the Stars, Screened: 1990, [1993]. [more yellow tape in boxes 47-53] (Box 8, Folder ID: 143.1263)
      Old number: EII4f, V.12.6516
      Director: Westmoreland, Joe
      Format: EII4f, V.12.6516
    - Title: Trojans: A Mind Over Motter Video, Screened: [1993]. [more yellow tape in boxes 47-53] (Box 8, Folder ID: 143.1264)
      Old number: EII4f, V.12.6521, 77
      Format: EII4f, V.12.6521, 77
    - Title: Mercury Rising, Screened: [1993]. [more yellow tape in boxes 47-53] (Box 8, Folder ID: 143.1265)
      Old number: EII4f, V.12.6523, 97
      Director: Manson, Portia
      Format: EII4f, V.12.6523, 97
    - Title: My Livingroom is a Theatre, Screened: [1993]. [more yellow tape in boxes 47-53] (Box 8, Folder ID: 143.1266)
      Old number: EII4f, V.12.6526, 103
      Director: Prietzel, Claudia
      Format: EII4f, V.12.6526, 103
    - Title: My Courbet…Or, A Beaver's Tale, Screened: [1993]. [more yellow tape in boxes 47-53] (Box 8, Folder ID: 143.1267)
      Old number: EII3b, V.12.6535, 235
      Director: Patten, Mary
      Format: EII3b, V.12.6535, 235
    - Title: [1.]--Sensual Men [2.]--Soapy Water, Screened: [1993]. [more yellow tape in boxes 47-53] (Box 8, Folder ID: 143.1268)
      Old number: EII3b, V.12.6539, 244
      Director: Bailer,N. Lee and Glowienke, Kurt
      Distributor: performers: [listed on accompanying letter]
      Format: EII3b, V.12.6539, 244
    - Title: [1.]--Girls Will Be Boys [2.]--Jill Jacks Off, [1.]--Screened: 1993. [more yellow tape in boxes 47-53] (Box 8, Folder ID: 143.1269)
      Old number: EII3b, V.12.6540
      Director: [1.]-- Kuhne, Kadet and Texas Tomboy
      Format: EII3b, V.12.6540
    - Title: Private Pleasures, Screened: 1993. [more yellow tape in boxes 47-53] (Box 8, Folder ID: 143.1270)
      Old number: EII3b, V.12.6543
      Director: Wow, O.
      Format: EII3b, V.12.6543
    - Title: Peanut, Screened: 1993. [more yellow tape in boxes 47-53] (Box 8, Folder ID: 143.1271)
      Old number: K7b, V.12.8728, 121
      Director: Jacobsen, Rick
      Format: K7b, V.12.8728, 121
    - Title: The Brenda And Glennda Show: Gender Cruise on the Circle Line - Part 2, Screened: 1993. [more yellow tape in boxes 47-53] (Box 8, Folder ID: 143.1272)
      Old number: K7d, V.12.8794
      Format: K7d, V.12.8794
    - Title: Kiev Blue, Screened: [1993]. [more yellow tape in boxes 47-53] (Box 8, Folder ID: 143.1273)
      Old number: EII3c, V.12.9100.C1
      Director: MacDonald, Heather
      Format: EII3c, V.12.9100.C1
    - Title: Lesbian and Gay Films and Videos From Brasil (Box 8, Folder ID: 143.1274)
      Old number: EII3e, V.12.9172
      Director: Cypriano, Tania
      Format: EII3e, V.12.9172
    - Title: Voices From the Front, Screened: [1993]. [more yellow tape in boxes 47-53] (Box 8, Folder ID: 143.1275)
      Old number: EII3e, V.12.9174
      Director: Hutt, Robyn, Elgear, Sandra and Meieran, David
      Distributor: performers: [listed in 1991 program]
      Format: EII3e, V.12.9174
    - Title: Down On The River, Screened: 1991 [more yellow tape in boxes 47-53] (Box 8, Folder ID: 143.1276)
      Old number: EII4c, V.34U.6416, 145
      Director: Stevens, Ylonda
      Format: EII4c, V.34U.6416, 145
    - Title: [1.]--Conceicao [2.]--Concepcion, Screened: [1993]. [more yellow tape in boxes 47-53] (Box 8, Folder ID: 143.1277)
      Old number: EII4c, V.34U.6417.C2
      Format: EII4c, V.34U.6417.C2
    - Title: Avid Tutorial Sample Footage (Box 9, Folder ID: 143.1239)
      Old number:
      Format: Betacam SP
    - Title: MIX Trailer 1993, Screened: [1993] (Box 9, Folder ID: 143.1240)
    - Title: Waking Up To Rape (Box 9, Folder ID: 143.1241)
      Old number: 6
      Duration: 40 minutes
    - Title: The Dreaming, Screened: 1993 (Box 9, Folder ID: 143.1244)
    - Title: Figment (Box 9, Folder ID: 143.1247)
      Old number: 7360
      Director: Sharits, Paul
      Format: Betacam
    - Title: Figment (Box 9, Folder ID: 143.1248)
      Old number: 7361
    - Title: Strut, Screened: [1993]. [more yellow tape in boxes 47-53] (Box 9, Folder ID: 143.1249)
      Old number: EII4b, V.12.6393, 306
    - Title: Deep Inside Porn Stars, Screened: 1993. [more yellow tape in boxes 47-53] (Box 9, Folder ID: 143.1250)
      Old number: EII4c, V.12.6426,
      Director: Club 90
      Distributor: performers: [listed in 1993 program]
    - Title: In Your Face With Amazing Grace (The Vatican is Burning), Screened: [1993]. [more yellow tape in boxes 47-53] (Box 9, Folder ID: 143.1251)
      Old number: EII4c, V.12.6437
    - Title: Mrs. Mouth Video Profile, Screened: 1993. [more yellow tape in boxes 47-53] (Box 9, Folder ID: 143.1252)
      Old number: EII4c, V.12.6438
      Director: Silverzweig, Paul
    - Title: American Fabulous, Screened: [1993]. [more yellow tape in boxes 47-53] (Box 9, Folder ID: 143.1253)
      Old number: EII4d, V.12.6446
      Director: Dakota, Reno
    - Title: Poof, Screened: 1994. [more yellow tape in boxes 47-53] (Box 9, Folder ID: 143.1254)
      Old number: EII4d, V.12.6455
      Director: Luketic, Robert
    - Title: The Cove Method, Screened: [1993]. [more yellow tape in boxes 47-53] (Box 9, Folder ID: 143.1255)
      Old number: EII4e, V.12.6486
      Director: Higginbottom, Mrs. and Westmorely, Joe
    - Title: Into The Light, Screened: [1993]. [more yellow tape in boxes 47-53] (Box 9, Folder ID: 143.1256)
      Old number: EII4e, V.12.6473, 55
    - Title: Butterfly Scavenger, Screened: [1993]. [more yellow tape in boxes 47-53] (Box 9, Folder ID: 143.1257)
      Old number: V.12.6486, 4
      Director: Morse, Barry
    - Title: Tales From the Watercloset, Screened: 1993. [more yellow tape in boxes 47-53] (Box 9, Folder ID: 143.1278)
      Old number: EII4c, V.34U.6419
      Director: Walsh, Susan and Marciniak, Kris
    - Title: Midwest Mambo, Screened: 1993. [more yellow tape in boxes 47-53] (Box 9, Folder ID: 143.1279)
      Old number: EII4d, V.34U.6456.C2
      Director: Everly, Bart
    - Title: A Hard Reign's Gonna Fall (Box 9, Folder ID: 143.1280)
      Director: Lance, Dean
    - Title: Fire! (Box 10, Folder ID: 143.1217)
      Director: Frilot-Harris
    - Title: Suburban Dykes, Screened: [1990] (Box 10, Folder ID: 143.1483)
      Director: Fatale
      Duration: [30] minutes
    - Title: AGORA, Screened: 1992 (Box 10, Folder ID: 143.1487)
      Old number: 50
      Director: Kinney, Robert and Donald
    - Title: BurLEZk II, Screening: Unknown (Box 10, Folder ID: 143.1515)
    - Title: Una Vuelta / A Ride Out, Screened: Unknown (Box 10, Folder ID: 143.1568)
      Director: Montoya, Ivonne Patricia
    - Title: Mein ist Dein Ganzes Herz, Screened: Unknown (Box 10, Folder ID: 143.1688)
      Old number: v.12.6480 E II 4 e 30
      Director: Gotz, Elke
    - Title: DeAundra Peek, Screened: Unknown (Box 10, Folder ID: 143.1720)
    - Title: [1.]-- Au Revoir, Shirlei [2.]-- Viva Eu!, Screened: Unknown (Box 10, Folder ID: 143.1740)
      Old number: 4C
    - Title: "Hunting Season", Screened: 1990, 1996 (Box 10, Folder ID: 143.1741)
      Old number: 4B
    - Title: [1.]-- The Earring [2.]-- Dyke After Dyke [3.]-- No Mirror [4.]-- Chancleteras, Screened: Unknown (Box 10, Folder ID: 143.1742)
      Old number: 4A
    - Title: [1.]-- Darkness of my Language [2.]-- Amorae [3.]-- Dyke After Dyke [3.]-- The Second Beast, Screened: Unknown (Box 10, Folder ID: 143.1743)
      Old number: 4D
    - Title: Ciudades de Lujuria (Cities of Lust), Screened: 1993 (Box 10, Folder ID: 143.1472)
    - Title: [1.]-- Diversion [2.]-- Song of the Goddess, Screened: [1993] (Box 10, Folder ID: 143.1605)
      Old number: 15
      Director: Pau, Ellen
      Duration: [60] minutes
    - Title: Ego Beach, Screened: [1993] (Box 10, Folder ID: 143.1643)
      Old number: 5
      Director: Kuhne, Lisa
    - Title: [1.]-- Kissy Suzuki Sucks [2.]-- No Glove / No Love [3.]-- And It's in Colour [4.]-- Inner Circle [5.]-- Pout Safer Sex TV Dinner, Screened: Unknown (Box 10, Folder ID: 143.1649)
    - Title: [1.]--The Last Time [2.]--Home You Go [3.]--Secrets, Screened: [1993] (Box 11, Folder ID: 143.1297)
      Old number: 498
      Director: Allen, Colette
    - Title: Shadows, Screened: 1993 (Box 11, Folder ID: 143.1298)
      Director: Caerage and Teri
    - Title: Quasi Una Fantasia, Screened: [1993] (Box 11, Folder ID: 143.1299)
      Director: Muller, Paul
    - Title: Greetings From Africa, Screened: [1993] (Box 11, Folder ID: 143.1301)
      Director: Dunye, Cheryl
    - Title: Anthology Film Archives Preservation Dinner Feb. 2, 1993 (Box 11, Folder ID: 143.1302)
      Director: Beroes, Stephanie
    - Title: [1.]--The Serenade [2.]--L'Ile de la Sagesse [3.]--[Imer?]telle, [2.]--Screened: 1993 (Box 11, Folder ID: 143.1303)
      Director: [2.]--de Monvel/Hayes, Genevieve Boutet
    - Title: Monsters In The Closet, Screened: 1994 (Box 11, Folder ID: 143.1304)
      Director: Reeves, Jennifer Todd
    - Title: She Thrills Me, Screened: 1993 (Box 11, Folder ID: 143.1305)
      Old number: 120
      Director: Bradley, Maureen
    - Title: Cholo Joto, Screened: 1993 (Box 11, Folder ID: 143.1306)
      Director: Robles, Augie
    - Title: [1.]--Sex Fish [2.]--Sex Bowl, [1.]--Screened: 1993 (Box 11, Folder ID: 143.1307)
      Director: [1.]--Maniac, E.T. Baby [2.]--Maniac, Baby
    - Title: The Flower Market, Screened: 1993, 1996 (Box 11, Folder ID: 143.1308)
      Director: Waters, Jack
    - Title: Amoeba Video Compilation: [1.]--Bitter Queen Blues [2.]--Workshop [3.]--It All Started In Black [4.]--We're Taking Over [5.]--Devil's Daughter (Box 11, Folder ID: 143.1309)
    - Title: Cell33, Screened: [1993] (Box 11, Folder ID: 143.1311)
      Director: Lopez, Vincent
    - Title: Negative Man: Give AIDS The Freeze, Screened: 1991 (Box 11, Folder ID: 143.1185)
      Director: Joritz, Cathy
      Duration: [180 minutes]
    - Title: Splash, Screened: 1996 (Box 11, Folder ID: 143.1200)
      Director: Harris, Thomas Allen
    - Title: Sisters in the Life: First Love, Screened: 1993 (Box 11, Folder ID: 143.1204)
      Director: Welbon, Yvonne
      Duration: 25 minutes
    - Title: I Never Danced The Way Girls Were Supposed To, Screened: 1992, 1996 (Box 11, Folder ID: 143.1215)
      Director: Suggs, Dawn
    - Title: Transeltown, Screened: 1993 (Box 11, Folder ID: 143.1228)
      Director: Paci, Myra
    - Title: Anik, Anne, Aurineide e Aline Vao a Praia (Un Filme Sin Cortes), Screened: 1993 (Box 11, Folder ID: 143.1467)
      Old number: #2 53327, EII4f, V.6512
      Director: Araujo, Jackson
    - Title: Il Mio Evore e un Vecello Cantore, Screened: Unknown (Box 11, Folder ID: 143.1686)
      Old number: 219
      Director: [Sanci, Claretta]
    - Title: [1.]-- Strapless [2.]-- The Candy Tangerine Man, Screened: Unknown (Box 11, Folder ID: 143.1690)
      Old number: K 7 d v.12.8788
      Director: [1.]-- Unknown [2.]-- [Cimber, Matt]
    - Title: [1.]-- A Call to Arms [2.]-- The Citadel, Screened: Unknown (Box 11, Folder ID: 143.1691)
      Old number: K 7 b v.12.8746
      Director: Swann, Cordelia
    - Title: Cut, Screened: Unknown (Box 11, Folder ID: 143.1704)
      Director: Camps, Liz
    - Title: Drawing the Line, Screened: [1992] (Box 11, Folder ID: 143.1731)
  - Subseries H: Ticket Sales
    - Box office records, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 489)
  - Subseries I: Outreach
    - Erato: International Lesbian and Gay Cultural News, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 490)
    - Neutral Zone newsletter, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 491)
    - Omni Ball invitation, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 492)
  - Subseries J: Grants/Fundraising
    - Funding research, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 493)
    - Grant samples - The Kitchen, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 494)
    - List of prospective grants, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 495)
    - AFI Independent Film and Videomaker Program, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 496)
    - Art Matters, Inc., 1993 (Box 5, Folder 497)
    - Benton Foundation, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 498)
    - Experimental Television Center, Ltd., 1993 (Box 5, Folder 499)
    - Funding Exchange - Paul Robeson Fund, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 500)
    - Colin Higgins Foundation, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 501)
    - Max and Anna Levinson Foundation, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 502)
    - Robert Mapplethorpe Foundation, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 503)
    - Joyce Mertz-Gilmore Foundation, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 504)
    - Philip Morris Companies, Inc., 1993 (Box 5, Folder 505)
    - New York Community Trust, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 506)
    - New York Council for the Humanities, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 507)
    - NYSCA - Correspondence, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 508)
    - NYSCA - Grant application, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 509)
    - Andy Warhol Foundation, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 510)
- SERIES VIII: 1994
  This series contains materials relating to the eighth year of the Festival.
  - Subseries A: Administrative Files
    - Administration/staff - Karim Ainouz hospitality badge, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 512)
    - Advertising tally, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 513)
    - Design plans for Anthology Film Archives, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 514)
    - Expenses - Budgets - Black Nations/Queer Nations?, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 515)
    - Expenses - Budgets - Pre-box, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 516)
    - Expenses - Financial summary (blank) (FOLDER MOVED), 1995 (Box 5, Folder 517)
    - Expenses - Invoices, bills, receipts, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 518)
    - Expenses - Invoices, bills, receipts, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 519)
    - Expenses - National Westminster Bank statements, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 520)
    - Expenses - Petty cash envelopes, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 521)
    - Expenses - Proposal for Mix trailer, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 522)
    - Festival statements - Call for ads/sponsorship, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 523)
    - Festival statements - Call for curators, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 524)
    - Festival statements - Newsletter, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 525)
    - Festival statements - Official invitation (blank), 1994 (Box 5, Folder 526)
    - Festival statements - Press release (inc. A Brief History of Mix, schedule of events, program info for Cyberqueer, Mix Brasil, and World Clique?), 1994 (Box 5, Folder 527)
    - Legal - Guest curator contract, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 528)
    - Legal - Vanessa Renwick, Toxic Shock exhibition contract, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 529)
    - Letterhead - Fax cover sheet (blank), 1994 (Box 5, Folder 530)
    - Letterhead - Festival letterhead, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 531)
    - Mailing lists - Committee contact information, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 532)
    - Mailing lists - Film index and filmmaker contacts, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 533)
    - Mailing lists - Misc. mailing list and print holdings information, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 534)
    - Notes - Advertising, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 535)
    - Notes - Budget, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 536)
    - Notes - Curators/submissions, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 537)
    - Notes - Development, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 538)
    - Notes - Distribution, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 539)
    - Notes - Hospitality, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 540)
    - Notes - Installations, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 541)
    - Notes - Lookout, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 542)